>> Jem Young: 如果你想看看谁
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if you wanna see who,
什么类型的， >> Jem Young: 谁允许黑客存在，
what type of,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Who allows hackers to exist,
对吧 ?
right?
这就是互联网我们遵循的规则
It's the internet,
there are certain rules we follow.
如果我输入所有帽子，那就意味着我在喊叫，如果我做了一个 /s，就意味着讽刺。
If I type in all caps, that means I'm
yelling, if I do a /s, that means sarcasm.
我们都知道这些规则。
We all know these rules.
为什么人们总是试图闯入我的服务器?
So why are people always trying
to break into my server?
或者，他们是从哪里来的 ?
Or, where are they coming from?
而攻击者主要来自世界上少数几个地方，
And attackers predominantly come
from a few places in the world,
如果你这么做就行了
where just these things are looks
as it's okay if you do this.
如果你想知道的话，我们可以像平常一样检查我们的 auth.log 。
If you wanna see that, we can check
our auth.log like we usually do.
我掏出了我的 IP 地址
I pulled mine, and I just pulled
a random IP address from there.
我要用 MaxMind GeoIP 数据库
And I'm gonna use
the MaxMind GeoIP database.
它告诉我袭击者是从中国的新加坡来的。
And it tells me that the attackers
came from Singapore in China.
而且主要是，这跟国家的文化没有关系，
And predominantly, this has nothing to
do with the culture of the countries or
任何类似的事情
anything like that.
但许多攻击事件往往来自俄罗斯，亚洲和美国。
But a lot of attacks tend to come from
Russia and Asia and the United States.
>> Jem Young: 我觉得有时候很有趣
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I just find it's
interesting sometimes, where like,
他们是怎么找到我的
how do they even find me?
我有时会看到一些来自朝鲜的东西，那是什么呢 ?
Sometimes I'll see some from North Korea,
which is like, what?
好吧，他们关心我什么 ?
[LAUGH] Okay, what do they care about me?
但是如果你很好奇，你可以去 maxmind.com/en/geoip-demo,
But if you're curious, you can go
to maxmind.com/en/geoip-demo, and
然后从您的 auth.log 中仅提取一个随机 IP 。
then pull just a random IP
from your from your auth.log.
看看这些袭击是从哪里来的
And just see where these attacks
are coming from in the world.
>> Jem Young: 说实话，我觉得他们都不愿意
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Honestly, I think it's
pretty brazen that they're not even gonna
隐藏他们的 IP 地址，因为他们不知道要做什么。
hide their IP address because they know
nothing's going to be done about it.
我可以向新加坡政府报告他们会是
I can report them to the Singapore
government, and they'll be like, yeah,
我们会调查的
we'll look into that.
不他们不会的
No, they won't.
> > Jem Young: 但似乎是一个有趣的国家。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: But
seems like an interesting country.
让我知道就像坦桑尼亚一样
Just let me know,
like Tanzania, or something.
这将是一个全新的，很酷的。
Cuz that would be a new one,
that would be cool.